Inventory of the John Elbert Elliott papers 1901-1980
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, subject file, and printed matter, 1915-1979
  - Printed matter
    - Oil industry
      - "American Association of Petroleum Geologists Foundation Issue: Selected Papers from East Coast Offshore Symposium,", 1973 (Folder 52: 7)
      - Directory of the Society of Mining Engineers of AIME, 1974 (Folder 52: 8)
      - "Registered Professional Engineers July 1974 Roster," Texas (Folder 52: 9)
    - Stanford, 1957-1978, undated (Folder 53: 1-3)
      General note
      See oil industry printed material for Stanford directories
  - Subject file
    - Herbert Hoover, undated (Folder 53: 4)
    - Herbert Hoover Presidential Library, 1975-1978 (Folder 53: 5)
      Includes correspondence of John M. Henry
    - Oil shale, 1965-1975 (Folder 53: 6)
- Motion picture film, 1971-1972 (Box 53)
  - "Rose Bowl 4th Quarter Highlights,", 1971-1972
    - Clipping, 1972 (Folder 53: 7)
    - Film, 1971-1972 (Film Shelf)
      Super 8 color film reel
- Oversize material, 1966-1980
  - GOP button, plastic tepee, plaque for Chevy Chase Center in Austin (1969), and USA Olympics bookends (1980) (Box 54)
  - Artwork with butterflies, undated (Box 55)
  - Drawings of Hoover Tower and Stanford campus, undated (Box 55)
  - Photograph of American Association of Petroleum Geologists, 1966 (Box 55)
  - Stanford calendars, 1979-1980 (Box 55)
  - Stanford University plaque, 1980 (Box 55)
    Gift to John Elliott from Welton Crook. Presented to the Stanford Club of Austin by Ruth Elliott
- Portrait of John Elliott painted by Engelhorn, oil painting